every time you open your phone you see
someone baking working out doing an
online course or turning into an
influence zone now with all the
socializing also online you may feel
fear of missing out when you see your
friends and peers being so active this
constant information is subconsciously
adding pressure pressure to be
productive pawns take this moment to
completely understand the situation
we're in we are all doing our best to
cope and coping looks different for
everyone for some it may be staying
productive while for others it may be
taking things soon there is no right or
wrong way off of them so here is my
suggestion give yourself a permission
slip to do nothing to do something to do
whatever makes you feel comfortable calm
and more importantly see start small set
out to do one thing a day and achieve
that acknowledge your small
accomplishments every day give yourself
some time to do an activity you enjoy
and don't forget you are doing your best
be proud more importantly be prepared
you can get a re Sahir the cheetah
[Music]